hi folks this is Matt and we're going to
嗨，大家好，我是马特，我们要
talk a little bit now about basing
现在说说基础
equilibrium and an equilibrium concept a
均衡和均衡概念
solution concept for Bayesian games and
贝叶斯游戏的解决方案概念和
the idea of this it's also sometimes
这个想法有时
referred to as Bayesian Nash equilibria
称为贝叶斯纳什均衡
the concept goes back to harsány John
这个概念可以追溯到harsányJohn
Harsanyi and in 98 1960s 1967 and 1968
哈桑尼（Harsanyi）和98年1960年代1967年和1968年
where he developed this concept and the
他在那里发展了这个概念，
idea is that that each player now you
想法是每个玩家现在
know when we're talking about a Bayesian
知道我们在谈论贝叶斯
game players have these types which
游戏玩家具有以下类型
determine their payoffs and relate to
确定他们的收益并与
the uncertainty and can actually tell
不确定性并可以真正说明
them something about what they expect
他们对他们期望的东西
other individuals types to be and an
其他个人类型为和
equilibrium now is can be a plan of
现在平衡可以是一个计划
action for each player as a function of
每个玩家的动作取决于
their types so it's going to say okay if
他们的类型，所以它会说，如果
I observed a certain type what am I
我观察到某种类型我是什么
going to do in the game and it should be
在游戏中要做，应该是
maximizing their expected utility so
最大化其预期效用，以便
it's going to be a best reply and what
这将是最好的答复，还有什么
are they expecting over well now instead
他们现在期望好吗
of just in just in the Nash equilibrium
在纳什均衡中
you fix the strategy of the other player
您确定其他玩家的策略
and then you just maximize your payoff
然后您就可以最大化您的收益
here we're expecting over the actions of
在这里，我们期待着
other players so here we've got a
其他玩家，所以在这里我们有一个
situation where we have to be figuring
我们必须要弄清楚的情况
out based on what we expect their types
根据我们期望的类型
to be and possibly what happened they
他们可能会发生什么
might be mixing how are they playing
可能会混合他们的演奏方式
based on those types what does that lead
根据这些类型，这会导致什么
to the expected action distribution
到预期的行动分配
you're going to face and in terms of the
您将要面对并就
types the other players types can
其他玩家类型可以的类型
actually also enter into your payoff
实际上也可以进入您的收益
function so your utility can depend on
功能，因此您的实用程序可以依靠
information that other people hold so it
其他人持有的信息
might be that somebody else knows about
可能是别人知道的
say the value of a stock and I'm trying
说股票的价值，我正在尝试
to invest based on what information and
根据什么信息进行投资
I have and I realize that I that other
我有，我意识到我
people are going to have other
人们将有其他
information and that information could
信息，该信息可以
affect the value to me as well of a
也会影响我的价值
particular asset for instance okay
例如特定资产好
so given a bayesian game we've got our
因此，考虑到贝叶斯游戏，我们有了
set of player's player's actions the
一组玩家的动作
type space probability distribution over
类型空间概率分布
the type space and
类型空间和
utility functions and for the
实用程序功能和
definitions we're going to provide here
我们将在此处提供的定义
we're going to take these to be finite
我们将这些视为有限的
sets of players finite sets of actions
一组玩家有限的动作
finite sets of types and finite sets of
类型的有限集和的有限集
strategies okay and when you start going
策略还可以，当您开始前进时
to infinite sets and continua you have
到无限集并连续
to be a little more careful about some
多一些注意
of the details of defining these things
这些东西的细节
and in particular measurability kinds of
特别是可测量性
considerations of an integration of
整合的考虑
things so we're going to stick with a
事情，所以我们要坚持一个
finite set where the basic principles
有限集的基本原理
and ideas will be fairly easy to
而且想法很容易
understand and extensions to these are
理解和扩展这些是
fairly straightforward although there's
相当简单，尽管有
some technical details you have to worry
您需要担心的一些技术细节
about ok pure-strategy what's a strategy
关于好的纯策略什么是策略
for a given player a player strategy now
对于给定的玩家，现在有一个玩家策略
is a mapping so S sub I which says as a
是一个映射，所以S sub I表示为
function of your type what's the action
您的类型的功能是什么
you're going to take that would be a
你将采取那将是
pure strategy in a sense that you're
从某种意义上说，纯策略
just picking an action for each type a
只是为每种类型选择一个动作
mixed strategy is then the obvious
那么混合策略就很明显
extension here where instead of picking
在这里扩展而不是选择
a pure action you're picking a
你在挑选一个纯粹的动作
probability distribution over actions as
动作的概率分布为
a function of your type and one thing
取决于您的类型和一件事
that's going to be useful then is that
那将是有用的，那是
if we have a particular type we can then
如果我们有一个特殊的类型，我们可以
talk about what the distribution over
说说什么分配
actions is so the mix under mixed
行动就是混合
strategy si by the person I plays what's
我扮演的人的策略si
the probability that action AI is going
动作AI进行的可能性
to be chosen by them if they happen to
如果他们碰巧被他们选择
be of type theta I so we use that
是theta类型的，所以我们用
notation and in some of their
符号和一些
calculations okay now when we start
现在开始计算就可以了
talking about Bayesian equilibrium now
现在谈论贝叶斯均衡
we have to talk about what a person's
我们必须谈论一个人的
expected utility is when they're making
预期的效用是他们制作时
their choices and there'll be different
他们的选择，会有不同
timing that we can think of so one is ex
我们可以想到的时机是前
ante
赌注
I have to form a plan for how I'm going
我必须为我的前进计划
to behave but I actually don't know
表现出来，但我实际上不知道
anything about anyone's type including
关于任何人类型的任何事情，包括
my own so we might think of this as for
我自己的，所以我们可能认为这是为了
instance you know a company forming a
例如，您知道一家公司成立了
long term plan for how it might say bid
关于如何说出价的长期计划
in a series of auctions that are coming
在即将进行的一系列拍卖中
but it hasn't actually gone out and
但实际上并没有熄灭，
collected information yet and it hasn't
收集信息还没有
actually seen the values of other
实际上看到了其他的价值
players or and so forth so it hasn't
玩家等等，所以没有
done any calculations but it's trying to
做任何计算，但它试图
form a strategy of how it's going to
形成如何发展的策略
behave second possibility interim stage
表现第二可能性过渡阶段
so a person knows something about her
所以一个人对她有所了解
his or her own type but not the types of
他或她自己的类型，但不是
other agents yet there are other players
其他特工还有其他球员
so this is a setting where you have seen
所以这是您所看到的设置
some part I've done my homework I know
我已经完成了一部分作业，我知道
what I've seen and I have to form a
我所看到的，我必须形成一个
strategy to bid in an auction but I
策略竞价，但我
don't know what the other players have
不知道其他玩家有什么
seen and that information could be
看到的信息可能是
valuable not only in determining what
不仅对确定什么有价值
their action is but also in determining
他们的行动还在于
whether or not I want to go ahead and
我是否要继续
follow a certain behavior or not based
遵循某种行为或不基于
on what my payoffs might be contingent
我的收益可能取决于
on what information they might have and
他们可能拥有的信息，以及
the third one is ex-post so everybody
第三个是事后，所以大家
knows everything about everybody's types
知道每个人的类型
now ex post is the relatively least
现在事后相对最少
interesting in in the basic sense of the
从基本意义上讲有趣
kinds of calculations we're going to be
我们将要进行的各种计算
doing because in that situation if the
这样做是因为在那种情况下
peoples are making their choices ex post
人民事后做出选择
then the game is going to boil down to
然后游戏将归结为
just the complete information games we
只是我们完整的信息游戏
had before now if people have to make
以前如果人们必须做
their choices that ex ante and they
他们事前的选择，他们
still want them to work ex post then
还是希望他们事后工作
that's a different story that we'll talk
我们要讲的是一个不同的故事
about a little later okay
大约过一会儿好
interim expected utility so let's talk
中期预期效用，让我们谈谈
about the expected utility that a player
关于玩家的预期效用
has if they're at the interim stage well
如果他们处于过渡阶段
we can say what does person I expect if
我们可以说我期望的人会怎样
they're of type theta I and the
它们是theta I和
strategies s are being followed and we
策略正在遵循，我们
end up with a calculation which looks as
最终得到一个看起来像
follows first of all we can look at what
首先，我们可以看看
the possible types are so we're going to
可能的类型是，所以我们要
be summing the person knows their type
总结这个人知道他们的类型
then that can tell them something about
那可以告诉他们一些有关
what they believe the probability of
他们相信什么
other people's types will be we're going
其他人的类型将是我们要去的
to sum across those things and the
总结这些东西，
utilities are going to be evaluated with
实用程序将与评估
respect to those types
尊重那些类型
so that's one aspect of it the second
这是第二个方面
aspect is that they also have to do the
方面是他们还必须
calculation of what they then believe
然后计算他们所相信的
other players will be doing or including
其他玩家将做或包括
themselves if they're mixing in terms of
他们自己，如果他们在混合方面
which actions will be chosen as a
哪些动作将被选为
function of the types so they have a
类型的功能，所以他们有一个
probability distribution over types then
然后按类型分布概率
what are the strategies that are going
有什么策略
to be played with what probability are
以什么概率玩
we going to see different actions and
我们将看到不同的动作，
then what's the utility of those actions
那这些动作的作用是什么
so we've got the payoff as a function of
所以我们得到的收益是
actions we've got probabilities of
我们有概率采取的行动
actions and we've got probabilities of
行动，我们有以下可能性
types okay and so that gives us an
输入还可以，因此
expected utility calculation which then
预期效用计算，然后
a player can use to evaluate what do
玩家可以用来评估做什么
they think a given strategy is going to
他们认为给定的策略将
lead to in terms of payoffs
导致收益
that's the interim expected utility if
这是中期预期效用，如果
we if we move things back and then have
如果我们把东西移回去，然后
to operate at an ex ante stage then we
事前操作，然后我们
can very simply say what does I think
可以很简单地说出我的想法
the probability is they'll be of
他们将成为
different types and what do they think
不同的类型，他们怎么看
their expected utility be as a function
它们的预期效用是一个函数
of those types that gives you an overall
这些类型可以使您整体
expected utility okay so we've got an ex
预期的实用程序好吧，所以我们有一个
ante expected utility which isn't going
事半功倍的预期效用
to condition on types and in an interim
根据类型和临时条件
one which conditions on types okay in
其中一种条件取决于类型
the ex post one they know exactly what
事发后他们确切知道什么
the types are so they can just evaluate
类型，以便他们可以评估
things directly as we did before okay so
就像我们之前所做的一样直接
the idea behind Bayes Nash equilibrium
贝叶斯·纳什均衡背后的思想
or Bayesian equilibrium the concept from
或贝叶斯均衡的概念
John Harr Sonya's work is that we're
John Harr Sonya的工作是
looking for a mixed strategy profile you
寻找混合策略配置文件
can also define pure strategy equilibria
也可以定义纯策略均衡
just by restricting to this to be pure
仅限于此而已
strategies as opposed to mixed but what
策略而不是混合策略，但是
has to be true is that each individual
必须真实的是，每个人
should be choosing a best response so
应该选择最佳的反应，这样
their strategy S sub I which is now a
他们的策略S sub I现在是
mapping from types into actions should
从类型到动作的映射应该
be maximizing their expected utility
最大化其预期效用
here taken at the interim stage so
这里是在过渡阶段
conditional on a theta I that they may
以theta为条件，他们可以
see and it should be true for every eye
看到，这对每只眼睛都是正确的
and every possible type so no matter
以及每种可能的类型，所以不管
what type I am I am the strategy I've
我是哪种类型，我就是我的策略
chosen should be maximizing my expected
选择应该最大化我的期望
utility given what I think other people
考虑到我认为其他人的效用
are going to do and giving the expected
要去做，给期望
utility that I'm calculating based on
我基于计算的实用程序
those strategies okay so this is exactly
这些策略还可以，所以这正是
analogous to Nash equilibrium it's just
类似于纳什均衡，只是
taking explicit account of the fact that
明确考虑到以下事实
individuals have will see different
个人会有不同的看法
things at different points in the at the
在不同点的东西
interim stage and should be maximizing
过渡阶段，应最大化
with respect to that information okay
关于那个信息还可以
the above definition this definition we
上面的定义这个定义我们
just went through is based on an interim
刚刚经历的是基于临时的
approach so it's asking that every
方法，所以它要求每个
individual maximize with respect to the
个人相对于
information that they have at the
他们在
interim stage and no matter what that
过渡阶段，无论那
information turns out to be and if if it
信息原来是，如果
happens to be true that every type
碰巧是每种类型
occurs with positive probability then
然后以正概率发生
this is also equivalent to just looking
这也相当于只看
at the ex-ante stage and saying look my
在事前阶段说我的
strategy should maximize my overall
策略应该使我的整体表现最大化
ex-ante expected utility because if it's
事前预期效用，因为如果
if it's maximizing things for every
如果它使每个人都最大化
possible theta then it's also going to
可能的θ然后它也将
maximize things when I average across
当我平均时，最大化事物
those Thetas and likewise if it didn't
那些Thetas，如果没有
maximize with respect to some theta and
关于某个θ最大化
all the Thetas are receiving positive
所有Thetas都收到积极
probability then it couldn't be
则不可能
maximizing overall so you can write this
最大化整体，所以您可以编写此
base in equilibrium down either from an
从一个
ex ante perspective or from an interim
事前观点或临时观点
perspective as long as all types have
只要所有类型都有
positive probability okay so what have
正概率好，那有什么
we got from Bayesian ash equilibria
我们来自贝叶斯灰平衡
we've got a extension of Nash
我们已经扩展了Nash
equilibrium to a setting to the Bayesian
贝叶斯环境的均衡
game setting it explicitly models
游戏设置它明确建模
behaviors and settings where we've got
我们所拥有的行为和设置
this uncertainty but the concept is
这种不确定性，但概念是
simple players choose strategies to
简单的玩家选择策略
maximize their payoffs in response to
最大化他们的回报以响应
others accounting for the these two
其他人占这两个
aspects of uncertainty one is strategic
不确定性方面是战略性的
uncertainty what do I think other
不确定性我怎么认为其他
players are going to be doing as a
玩家将作为
function of types and uncertainty and
类型和不确定性的函数
kindly pay off uncertainty I've got to
请偿还我必须承担的不确定性
be expecting over types which might
期待可能的类型
enter my payoffs
输入我的收益
so it's capturing both of those elements
因此它捕获了这两个元素